Hello! These are my simple interest calculator programs coded in Java, Python, and C#.  Feel free to look at each program!


Some things I learned coding these programs:

1. I learned how to format decimal values into currency format in python.
2. I just started with C# the day of coding simpleInterest.cs so it was pretty easy to grasp because of my experience with Java. TL,DR; C# is not as bad as I thought.


Some things that I would like to learn now:
1. how to format strings in C#, looking over the documentation, its fairly different from both python and java and I'll have to learn.
2. how ofhte primitive and reference types work in C#, I will gain more exposure in my next programs so I'll keep everyone updated!



THANKS FOR VIEWING, AND KEEP ON CODING!!!


  _____           _           _      _        ____   
 |  __ \         | |         (_)    | |      |  _ \  
 | |__) |___   __| | ___ _ __ _  ___| | __   | |_) | 
 |  _  // _ \ / _` |/ _ \ '__| |/ __| |/ /   |  _ <  
 | | \ \ (_) | (_| |  __/ |  | | (__|   <    | |_) | 
 |_|  \_\___/ \__,_|\___|_|  |_|\___|_|\_\   |____(_)
                                                   
                                                   
 



